(Raj:)Hey, look at me, I don't have a foreskin.
(Howard:)Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Are you aware that your sister
is an incredibly attractive woman?
(Sheldon:)Hm.
She has the symmetry and low body fat
that Western culture deems desirable.
It's noteworthy that at other points
in history...
(Sheldon:)...heavier women were the standard for
beauty because girth suggested affluence.
- That's fascinating...
- I didn't say fascinating.
(Sheldon:)I said it was noteworthy.
All right. Noted.
(Leonard:)But my point
is that Koothrappali and Wolowitz...
(Leonard:)They're hitting on your sister.
Ugh. It's...
(Sheldon:)Oh. Okay. You know, I don't want
to criticize your rhetorical style...
...but we'd be further along
in this conversation...
(Sheldon:)...if you'd begun with that thought.
(Leonard:)That's great, but...
We took quite a detour
from what I understand to be your thesis.